<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on The Shattered Lands of Tu&#39;um  Mundi</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on The Shattered Lands of Tu&#39;um  Mundi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bright Queen Thela</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/nations/dragons/bright-queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/nations/dragons/bright-queen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The large domain of the Bright Queen Thela, mostly covered by the Thel Forest. The fast flowing Strik River runs through it&amp;rsquo;s center and connects its largest cities. It&amp;rsquo;s northern edge disappears into the Void.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;population&#34;&gt;Population&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The land has a population of just over a million people total spread throughout several hundred towns and burgs, most of which are unnamed, and a few dozen large towns and less than five major cities.&#xA;Thel Forest  is populated mostly by elves  living in their ancestral homes, with the edges of the forest colonized by  Humans .&#xA;The mountains to the north and to the west are homes to distinct clans of  Dwarves .&#xA;The plains to the northeast are homes to families of  Halflings  while the hills to the southwest are homes to  Gnomes .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dizazhra Mountain People</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/nations/free-peoples/dizazhra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/nations/free-peoples/dizazhra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Though the Smith King and his people rule in the Dizazhra Mines, overhead, the mountain folk remain independent, with dozens of distinct tribes. They have a long history of warring for land and resources. However, when foreign groups try to invade, many  tribes will ally and mount a dangerous defnse. With access to high quality steel at the surface, they have often enjoyed superior weaponry and armor, and in the post shattering have tightly kept secret techniques for making advanced firearms and gunpowerder&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organized Faiths</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/faith/organized/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/faith/organized/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;draconic-cults&#34;&gt;Draconic Cults:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The largest group of faithful are dragon worshippers. Going by many names and each with their own unique creeds, followers worship the ancient dragons, seeking out mighty works and old wisdom. Some of them latch on to a modern dragon as a connection to the ancients, elevating them to a divine creature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;crown&#34;&gt;Crown:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second largest faith, they believe those with Crowns are living gods, divine beings with unimaginable power they use to shape the world to their liking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Races</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/character-creation/races/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/character-creation/races/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fill this out when we decide what system to use&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm Riders</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/nations/free-peoples/storm-riders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/nations/free-peoples/storm-riders/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DM! DM! Can I be one of these guys??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course! As you can see, there is very little info below, just ask me for more info and I&amp;rsquo;ll send you more lore, and we can figure out why your not chilling in the clouds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Extremely little is known about these peoples.In the modern period, the Storm Riders seem closer to a large cult than they do an esteemed civilization. They hide in the clouds and are essentially unknown to the rest of the world. They worship a god they call Sturm, and wield powerful  magics based on storms. Lightning, wind, and rain are their favored materials.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Witch King</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/nations/dragons/witch-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/nations/dragons/witch-king/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin Cities</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/nations/free-peoples/twin-cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/nations/free-peoples/twin-cities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two cities whose hearts are seperated by a days carriage ride on paved stone, their outskirts stretch to touch each other, intermingling in the middle. Their centers are guarded by two sets of walls and dozens guard towers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The southern city is called Port Miracle, situated on the Gulf of Miracle it started as a collection of fishing towns, with a high amount of trade. They combined and built a fort to protect themselves and continued to grow, eventually expanding outside their defensive walls.&#xA;The northern city is called Siegetown. It started as the military camp for a three year siege against Port Miracle by the Tricorn King. Now, it is home to many schools of combat and the city has a deep history of martial prowess.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
