<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faith on The Shattered Lands of Tu&#39;um  Mundi</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/faith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faith on The Shattered Lands of Tu&#39;um  Mundi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/faith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Organized Faiths</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/faith/organized/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/faith/organized/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;draconic-cults&#34;&gt;Draconic Cults:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The largest group of faithful are dragon worshippers. Going by many names and each with their own unique creeds, followers worship the ancient dragons, seeking out mighty works and old wisdom. Some of them latch on to a modern dragon as a connection to the ancients, elevating them to a divine creature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;crown&#34;&gt;Crown:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second largest faith, they believe those with Crowns are living gods, divine beings with unimaginable power they use to shape the world to their liking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Voice of the World</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/faith/votw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/faith/votw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A mysterious force exists in the world, perhaps the closest things to actual gods that exist in the Shattered Lands. There seem to be spirits of a kind that inhabit the lands, and sometimes they can speak to the mortals of this world. For most the speech is incomprehensible, closer to a random feeling they get nudging them one way or another, but sometimes the spirit speaks up, and its voice can be heard like a whisper deep in your head.&#xA;This manifests in different ways. Perhaps somewhere in a city, violence is going to take place, folks might hear the city telling them to avoid a certain street. A forest might whisper of the monster that lurks deep within, or a mountain might carry word of what it sees on top of its peak.&#xA;It takes practice to be able to hear the voice at will, most people will likely only hear it a few times in their life when it is loud, and they are unlikely to comprehend or know they&amp;rsquo;ve heard it at all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
