<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dragons on The Shattered Lands of Tu&#39;um  Mundi</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dragons on The Shattered Lands of Tu&#39;um  Mundi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Centra</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/centra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/centra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The land of The Witch King. Entirely made up of the foothills stretching from the Dizazrha mountains to the barrier mountains around the Rot Queen&amp;rsquo;s land.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lomb</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/lomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/lomb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The land of The Sword King. Before Solomon took the Crown from the previous dragon 12 years ago, the land was a conglomerate of city states that operated as a single nation. Now, the city states are isolated and fearful of each other, and all answer to the King.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The vasts majority of Lomb is covered by the Candlestick Dunes, large pillars of stone that dot an otherwise flat landscape. Cities and settlements are mostly built into the pillars with small towns dotted throughout the dunes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mithral</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/mithral/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/mithral/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The land of the Smith King. Hundreds, perhaps even thousands of miles of tunnels and caverns. Some carved by hand, some carved by dragons, and some developed from natural forces. Dwarves have spread through the entire area under the Dizazrha mountain range. They mostly gather in massive cities. They organize into clans, loosely connected by blood and bond.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Smith King&amp;rsquo;s influence covers the entire mountain range. Under his protection and governed by his hand selected council of ministers. Many skilled craftsmen create weapons and armor from precious minerals found int he mountains.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thel</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/thel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/geography/dragons/thel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thel, the large domain of the Bright Queen Thela, mostly covered by the Thel Forest. The fast flowing Strik River runs through it&amp;rsquo;s center and connects its largest cities. It&amp;rsquo;s northern edge disappears into the Void.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;population&#34;&gt;Population&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The land has a population of just over a million people total spread throughout several hundred towns and burgs, most of which are unnamed, and a few dozen large towns and less than five major cities.&#xA;Thel Forest  is populated mostly by elves  living in their ancestral homes, with the edges of the forest colonized by  Humans .&#xA;The mountains to the north and to the west are homes to distinct clans of  Dwarves .&#xA;The plains to the northeast are homes to families of  Halflings  while the hills to the southwest are homes to  Gnomes .&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
